# **Alberto Ramirez Salas**

Highly skilled and versatile Software Developer with experience in a wide range of technologies. I specialise in creating modern and scalable web, mobile applications and video games

+34 628 49 21 58 github.com/arsalas linkedin.com/in/alberto-ramirez-salas albertoramirezsalas.com

a.ramir.sa@gmail.com

## **Relevant Experience**

## Software Developer at Freelance Sep 2022 — Present

- Build, style, and ship high-quality web apps, design systems, mobile apps and video games for a diverse array of clients using technologies such as JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Vue, NodeJs, Unreal Engine and more.
- Private teacher for students who want to improve their Knowledge.
- Teach and mentor students.

## Full Stack Developer at AvantgardelT Jul 2023 — Nov 2023

- Develop new features at Front End Platform.
- Fix bugs in others features.
- Create new features at Back End REST Api.
- Use Vue with Quasar for build user interfaces
- Use NestJS and PrismaORM for build REST Api.

## **Lead Teacher** at **Ironhack** Sep 2022 — Nov 2022

- Lead a team of instructors at Front End Bootcamp with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Vue.js and Git.
- Developing and executinf comprehensive lesson plans.
- Delivering dynamic and interactive classes.

# Full Stack Developer at Social Labs Jan 2020 — Aug 2021

- Migrate to a web app admin panel for an enterprise application.
- Build new features at admin panel for a hotel chain app.
- Created a marketplace application with an admin panel for stores, enabling secure orders from suppliers and payments via bank credit.
- Build database procedures.

# Web Developer at Captura Electronica Oct 2019 — Nov 2019

- Design and develop the admin panel user interface.
- Implementing server-side logic for data managment.
- Connecting the admin panel to the MySQL database.

#### Skills

**Programming Languages** 

JavaScript/TypeScript, HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL, C/C++

#### **Libraries & Frameworks**

Vue, React, Node.js, React Native, NestJS, Express.js, Electron, Socket.io, Tailwind CSS, Unreal Engine

#### **Tools & Platforms**

Git, GitHub, Docker

## **Selected Projects**

#### **DaVinci Awards**

Web app to make and judge contest for employers Amazon

#### **Parcheesi**

Parcheesi game for Arcade

#### **Educations**

#### 42 Barcelona

Software Developer

#### Ilerna

Certificate of Higher Education in Web applications development

#### **iDesigner**

Master in video games design and programming with Unreal Engine

#### Languages

Spanish - Mother tongue Catalan - Mother tongue English - Intermediate